{
  "shortDescription": "Test your knowledge of swords from around the world.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Which sword is Japanese?",
      "answers": ["Katana", "Saber", "Rapier"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which sword is Persian?",
      "answers": ["Shamshir", "Claymore", "Gladius"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which sword is European?",
      "answers": ["Rapier", "Dao", "Kris"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which sword is Chinese?",
      "answers": ["Dao", "Tachi", "Scimitar"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which sword is Scottish?",
      "answers": ["Claymore", "Khopesh", "Jian"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which sword is Roman?",
      "answers": ["Gladius", "Katana", "Zweihander"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which sword is Arabian?",
      "answers": ["Scimitar", "Bokken", "Cutlass"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which sword is Indian?",
      "answers": ["Kris", "Katana", "Rapier"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which sword is Filipino?",
      "answers": ["Kris", "Saber", "Estoc"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which sword is Viking?",
      "answers": ["Ulfberht", "Shamshir", "Jian"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which sword is German?",
      "answers": ["Zweihander", "Khopesh", "Dao"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which sword is Egyptian?",
      "answers": ["Khopesh", "Cutlass", "Tanto"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which sword is French?",
      "answers": ["Rapier", "Katana", "Kris"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which sword is British?",
      "answers": ["Claymore", "Dao", "Saber"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which sword is used by pirates?",
      "answers": ["Cutlass", "Bokken", "Jian"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which sword is Korean?",
      "answers": ["Hwando", "Saber", "Rapier"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which sword is used by samurai?",
      "answers": ["Katana", "Gladius", "Scimitar"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which sword is used by ninjas?",
      "answers": ["Ninjato", "Saber", "Rapier"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which sword is used in fencing?",
      "answers": ["Rapier", "Dao", "Shamshir"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which sword is a two-handed weapon?",
      "answers": ["Zweihander", "Dao", "Cutlass"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    }
  ]
}
